get apron
wear apron
switch on oven
pick up plates
open cupboard
put plates
pick up plate
put plate
pick up tupperware
close drawer
open drawer
put Tupperware
close drawer
pick up two stainers
open cupboard
put stainers
pick up pot
pick up lid
cover pot
pick up pot
put pot
close cupboard
pick up pan
put pan on stove
pick up bag
open trash bin
throw bag
pick up wooden spoon
pick up knife
pick up cutlery
open drawer
put spoons
put knife
put wooden spoon
close drawer
wear gloves
pick up sponge
open tap
put liquid
pick up tupperware
open tap
rinse tupperware
wash tupperware
still washing tupperware
open tap
rinse tupperware
close tap
put tupperware
pick up tupperware
wash lid
rinse lid
put lid
pick up spoon
wash spoon
pick up knife
wash knife
Pick up spoon
wash spoon
pick up spoon
pick up fork
wash fork
pick up spoon
wash spoon
open tap
rinse cutlery
put spoon
rinse fork
put fork
rinse spoons
put spoon
in a spoon
rinse knife
put knife
pick up mug
open tap
rinse mug
close tap
put mug
pick up plate
wash plate
open tap
rinse plate
close tap
put plate
pick up plate
wash plate
open tap
rinse plate
close tap
put plate
open tap
rinse mug
close tap
put mug
pick up mug
pick up plate
put plate
fill mug
put mug
pick up plate
wash plate
Open tap
Rinse plate
Close tap
Put plate
Pick up mug
Put mug
Pick up plate
Wash plate
Open tap
Rinse plate
Close tap
Put plate
Empty sink
Empty water from sink
Still emptying sink
Open tap
Sprinkle water
Close tap
Empty sink
take off gloves
open cupboard
get stainer
put stainer
open fridge
get tomato
put tomato in stainer
then put in tomato
return tomato to fridge
pickup lettuce
pickup cucumber
close fridge
pickup stainer
put strainer
remove leaves from lettuce
open bin
throw leaves
close bin
put lettuce
open drawer
get knife
remove plastic cover from cucumber
put cover
open tap
wash cucumber
close tap
pick up strainer
wash tomatoes
Close tap
Pick up chopping board
Put chopping board
Put strainer on chopping board
Pick up lettuce
Remove leaves from lettuce
Put leaves in strainer
Remove leaf
Put leaf
Open trash bin
Throw close trash bin
Pick up strainer
Wash lettuce
Close tap
Shake strainer
Pick up chopping board
put chopping board
move cup
pick up plate
put wooden salad plate
pick up lettuce
put lettuce on chopping board
put lettuce
pick up lettuce
remove end of tomato
put stainer
pickup tomato
remove end
put tomato
pickup tomato
pickup
remove
put
pickup
pickup tomato
remove end of tomato
put tomato
pickup stainer
Puts dinner next to sink
Pickup knife
Chop lettuce using knife on chopping board
Chop lettuce
Pickup chopped lettuce
Put lettuce in salad plate
Pick lettuce
Put lettuce
Chop end of cucumber
Slice cucumber
Slice cucumber using knife
“chop cucumber”
“chop cucumber using knife on chopping board”
“pick up chop cucumber”
”put cucumber in plate”
“pick up cucumber”
“put cucumber “
“put cucumber”
“pick up cucumber “
“pick up chopping board”
“put chopping board in sink”
“pick up dough”
“pick up leather”
“open cupboard”
Remove Packaging
Pick up sweet corn can
Pick up can
Look at can
Return can
Close cupboard
Put can
Remove Ladder
Put towel
Open can
Open Tap
Rinse sweet corn
Open tap
Fill can with water
Rinse sweet corn
Put sweet cornon salad
Put can
Mix Salad
Using hands mixing salad
Open can
Throw can
Open tap
Wash hands
Pick up towel
Dry hands
Open cupboard
Get tray
Close cupboard
Move tray
Put tray
Open freezer
Open drawer
Close drawer
Get box
Read on box
Open box
Put chicken burger on tray
Return books to drawer
open drawer
get bag
Open bag
read on bag
pick up potato
put potato on in three
close bag
pick up bag
return bag
open bag
get onion rings
put onion rings on tray
cook onion rings
close bag
put back
close drawer
close freezer
pick up tray
open bin
close bin
open oven
put tray
close oven
set timer
open cupboard
get vinegar
get herbs
get herb
put herb on salad
sprinkle herb
sprinkle another herb
put herb
put vinegar
close herb
put back herb
put back vinegar
move pasta
return pasta
search
searching
pick up olive oil
put olive oil or sprinkle olive oil on salad
put olive oil on salad
empty olive oil can
close olive oil bottle
open trash bin throw olive oil
open fridge
pick up olives
put olives on side
open fridge
return olives
close fridge
dry hands
wear gloves
get sponge
return sponge
pick sponge
put liquid
Wash chopping board
Open Tap
Rinse chopping board
Return chopping board
Open Tap
Wash tap
Wash mug
Close tap
Put mug
pick up knife
wash knife
Pick up strainer
Wash Strainer
pick open tap
rinse strainer
close tap
put strainer
open tap
rinse knife
close tap
put knife
look around
pick up bags
open trash can
throw bags
pick up water filter
pick up cup
fill water
drink water
close cupboard
open tap
hold and fill water filter
close tap
put water filter
[END SUBTITLE]